

Mohsen Hosseini

E-mail: mail@mohsenhosseini.info **Website:** https://mohsenhosseini.info

Phone: 00989192792373

SUMMERY

As a programmer, I have 5 years experience on web developing with PHP language and 2 years experience on microcontroller programming (AVR) with c and c++. I have experience in startup environments and been part of the great agile team on fast-growing startup, and familiar with the business plan, marketing, and agile methodology. Interested in teamwork and care about my teammates and share knowledge, it would always better to work alongside a motivated team. For the summary of languages and technologies, I have worked with I can name: PHP, Laravel, Lumen, ReactJs, MySQL, Eloquent, Redis, Linux, Docker, Git, Gitlab CD/CI, Apache, Bash. and summary of CMS has developed plugins form them I can name: Magento, WordPress, WHMCS, OpenCart, PrestaShop, Joomla

TOP SKILS

PHP7, Laravel, Lumen, ReactJs, Mysql, Redis

WORK EXPERIENCE

Becopay Co.

2018 — Present

Web developer

Becopay service is established to facilitate cryptocurrency payments in Iran. Buyers can pay with any cryptocurrency and merchants receive their money on their bank account. **Website:** www.becopay.com/en

The things I did

- Designed the company website
- Developing the php pakage and plugins for must of the e-commerce cms and dockerized them for easy use.
- Installed and customized the crm for company
- Installed and configuration gitlab CD/CI and Gitlab runner for projects

Hamavaran Co 2017 — 2018

Web developer

Back-end developer at Hamavaran information & communications processing (ICP). **website:** www.hamavaran.com

Some technology used here: Laravel, Lumen, Redis, MySql, MongoDB, ReactJS

Project:

Varzeshavval mobile application

The football livescores app with scores, news, tables, fixtures, Media gallery and much more from Premier League, Bundesliga, Liga BBVA, MLS and many more.

- Setareha Website
 Social media website with share media, poll and game
- StarLand website

Mohsen Hosseini

Social media website with share media about celebrities

Ocean content management panel

The ocean panel is managing the applications users and contents.

VasVitrin

Browse and download all of the company apps

STEx Co 2014 — 2017

Co Founder & Software Developer

This company designing and developing software and hardware which use on industrial and

home automation

this is the some of the device we designed on this company:

gsm controller device

this device use for remote controlling and monitoring by sms & voice call

Traffic Control System

This device controlling and monitoring by Network and RF remote

Access Control & Security system

this device use for remote controlling and monitoring by GSM and RF remote

Remote load Break Switch Controller

This device use for remote controlling and monitoring by GSM , Network and according to the

standard SCADA protocol (like modbus) and sync with SCADA Software

Smart water sales device

This device sales the water with the RFID cards

MAPS Technology Center

December 2015 — February 2016

Web developer

In branch of MAPS Technology Center located in Zanjan Science & Technology Park people

tried to build infrastructure of a big IT company which can serve international IT services.

developing the booking system wordpress plugin

K.H.M.SH co 2013 — 2014

Web developer

K.H.M.SH (kavoshgaran hoshe masoni shomal garb) is a web developer company, Tabriz

Designing and developing the hospital portal on there.

EDUCATION

Islamic Azad University-Zanjan

2010 - 2015

Computer Engineering, Software

INTERESTS

Linux

B.S

- Photography
- New technology

CERTIFICATE

- World Entrepreneurship forum iran
 Certificate of participation, August 2015
- Certificate of Skill

Web designer and developer, 2013

Mohsen Hosseini 2

Certificate of Skill php programer , 2012

LANGUAGES

- English(Good ability of listening, writing, reading and speaking)
- Persian (Native Speaker)

Mohsen Hosseini 3